本作品之片源来自互联网，仅供学习、交流之用。请自觉于下载后24小时内删除。任何组织和个人不得用于任何商业用途，否则一切后果请自行承担！如果喜欢本片，请购买正版
听着  老爸  你还记着我老特想去的那个冒险天地吧
Okay, dad, so you know how I always want to go to super adventure land.
但你老说太贵了
But you tell me it's too expensive,
即使冒险天地物超所值
Even though it's totally worth it
因为它是地球上最好玩的地方
'cause it's the funnest place on earth?
记得
Yes.
现在好了  问题解决了
Well, problem solved.
“此赠券  可抵消五美元的
"this coupon, good for $5 off admission price.
冒险天地门票价格
To super adventure land.
但需要先在杰森杂货店消费一百元
Upon $100 purchase at Jensen's groceries,
此赠券周二至周日无效
Not valid Tuesday through Sunday,
杂货店周一关门停业”
Closed Monday."
想法不错
Nice try.
但是  老爸
But, dad,
他们新添了一个新游戏  叫做糖果风暴
They have this new ride called the storm twizzler.
十个人里面有九个人玩后都会呕吐
Nine out of 10 people barf on it.
他们甚至还会给你拍呕吐照
They even take your photo.
盖比  要是我彩票中奖了
Gabe, I'll take you to super adventure land.
我就带你去冒险天地
Just as soon as I win the lottery.
噢  嘿  说到彩票
Oh, hey, speaking of which,
也许今天就是你的幸运日
Maybe today is your lucky day.
很有可能啊  看一看
Could be. Let's take a look.
嘿  是个七  对吧
Hey, there's a seven, right?
-是的  -不错啊
-Yeah. -That's pretty good.
嘿  再看看这个  又是一个七
Hey, look at this. We got another seven.
有戏啊    再来个七  我们就
That's not too bad. One more seven... we got...
噢  看啊  噢  看啊  噢
Oh, look at... oh, look at... oh!
你去不成了
You're not going.
■
本字幕由★迪幻字幕组★为您奉献
欢迎登录 www.Deefun.com
生活搞得一团糟
<i>Today's all burnt toast </i>
就要迟到  爸爸在叫
<i>Running late, and dad jokes</i>
我左脚的鞋子有没有人看到
<i>Has anybody seen my left shoe</i>
■
翻译： Johnny-Z
我闭上眼  咬口早餐
<i>I close my eyes, take a bite</i>
跳上车子  放声大笑
<i>Grab a ride, laugh out loud</i>
哎呀  老爸  鞋子就在房顶上
<i>There it is up on the roof</i>
■
校订： line
我也曾这样生活  我已经顺利走过
<i>I've been there, I've survived</i>
所以听取我的建议
<i>So just take my advice</i>
■
后期： Johnny-Z  sarina
宝贝  不要放弃
<i>Hang in there, baby</i>
世界有很多疯狂无奈
<i>Things are crazy</i>
可是我知道你会有美好将来
<i>But I know your future's bright</i>
宝贝  不要放弃
<i>Hang in there, baby</i>
不要怀疑
<i>There's no maybe</i>
一切终会如你所愿
<i>Everything turns out all right</i>
生活有悲有喜
<i>Your life is up and down</i>
但是请相信我  坚持就有好结果
<i>But trust me it comes back around</i>
你会喜欢将来的你
<i>You're gonna love</i> <i>who you turn out to be</i>
宝贝  不要放弃
<i>Hang in there, baby.</i>
查莉成长日记  第二季第十六集
Good Luck Charlie  S02E16  Monkey Business
嘿  老妈
Hey, mom.
嘿  宝贝  来见见咱们的新邻居
Hey, honey. Come meet our new neighbor.
这是我的女儿  泰迪
This is my daughter Teddy.
我叫德比·杜利  你好啊
Debbie Dooley. How're you doing?
我好得很  德比·杜利女士
I'm doing dandy, Debbie Dooley.
德比和她的丈夫道格刚从爱荷华州搬过来
Debbie and her husband Doug just moved here from Iowa.
道格是我们新的副警长
Doug's our new deputy police chief.
而且他们还有一个和查莉同龄的女儿
And they have a daughter Charlie's age.
-迪迪·杜利  -噢
-Deedee dooley. -Oh.
德比明天需要个临时保姆
Debbie needed a babysitter for tomorrow.
于是我就把你介绍给她了
And I was just telling her how terrific you are.
噢  是吗  恐怕不成  其实我朋友艾薇和我
Oh yeah. No, actually my friend Ivy and I.
明天要带查莉去“填充猴儿”
Were gonna take Charlie to make-a-monkey tomorrow.
而且我们会很乐意带迪迪一起去的
And we'd be happy to bring deedee along.
什么是“填充猴儿”
What's make-a-monkey?
噢  解释起来有点儿复杂  就是有个地方
Oh, it's kind of complicated. It's this place where you...
可以让你  填充  猴儿  我
You make... A monkey. I...
我觉着这解释起来也不是很复杂
I guess it's not that complicated.
噢  我想问一下
Oh, I meant to ask...
你的狗在哪
Where is your dog?
我们没有狗
We don't have a dog.
但是隔壁那位好心的达布尼太太告诉我
But that nice Mrs. Dabney next door told me.
小心盖比
To beware of Gabe.
盖比是我儿子
Gabe is my son.
她说盖比咬过她
But she said he bit her...
而且还在她的草坪上小便
And went to the bathroom on her lawn.
他们之间的关系很微妙
They have a very unique relationship.
欢迎入住本街区
Welcome to the neighborhood.
噢  我觉着这块儿应该
Oh, I think this one goes...
不对
No.
噢  是不是应该
Oh, doesn't this one go...?
不是
No.
呃  算了吧  一会查莉会帮咱们拼好的
Eh, forget it. Charlie can help us with it later.
噢  我爸爸在外面呢  我该走了
Oh, my dad's outside. I gotta go.
-他不喜欢等人  -好吧
-He doesn't like to be kept waiting. -All right.
-再见  -再见
-See ya. -See ya.
难怪我们拼不出来  这只适用于一至三岁的儿童
No wonder we couldn't do it. It's for ages one to three.
你是PJ
You P.J.?
呃  是的  是的  是我
Uh, y-yeah yeah. That's me.
那你觉着和一个女孩开始约会后
So you start going out with a girl.
见见她的父亲就不重要了吗
And you don't think it's important to meet the father?
噢  十分抱歉
Oh, I'm sorry.
让我很费解的是  你脑子里是怎么想的
Makes me wonder what's going on inside your head.
相信我  先生
Trust me, sir,
我脑子里什么也没想
There's nothing going on in here at all.
我会一直盯着你的
I'm gonna be watching you.
来确保你是否对斯凯勒真情实意
To make sure you treat Skyler right,
是否配得上她
That you're worthy of her.
还有一件事  我不想让她知道
One more thing: I don't want her to know
我正在对你进行审查
I've been checking up on you.
好吧  那她认为你现在干嘛呢
Well, what does she think you're doing right now?
借用洗手间
Using the bathroom.
您还有别的事情吗
Is there anything else?
通常我用洗手间的时间比较长
Usually it takes me a while to use the bathroom.
-嘿  来吧  -嘿
-Hey, dad. -Hey.
噢  老爸  你东西掉了
Oh, dad, I think you dropped something.
噢  嘿  我的刮刮卡
Oh, hey, one of my scratchers.
噢  拭目以待吧  也许能中大奖
Oh, hey, let's see. Maybe we've won.
七
Seven.
又是七
Another seven.
以前也是如此  最后一个号码也懒的看了
Been here before. And the last number.
怎么了
What?
看啊  是个七  是七
Look, it's a seven. It's a seven.
-中了  中了  -中了多少钱
-I won. I won. -How much did you win?
一百万
$1 million!
呜  呜
Whoo-hoo!
我  我  我发了  我发了  我发了
Whoo! Whoo! I won, I won, I won!
老爸犯什么病呢
What is going on with dad?
他以为他中了彩票
He thinks he won the lottery.
-以为  -是啊  我逗他玩呢
-Thinks? -Yeah, it's a prank.
我从恶搞商店买了一张假的刮刮卡
I bought one of those fake scratchers from the joke store.
他还真上当了
He fell for that?
呜  呜  我是世界之王
<i>Whoo-hoo!</i> <i>I'm king of the world!</i>
他会发现的
He's gonna find out.
没错  大不了就接受两周的禁闭惩罚
Yeah, and I'll be grounded for two weeks.
但是  知道吗  那时我已经从冒险天地回来了
But, you know, I'll have been to super adventure land.
我已权衡利弊  这绝对值了
It's worth it. I crunched the numbers.
我这叫一个美啊  我都不知道该干啥了
I'm so happy, I don't know what to do with myself.
是吗  昨天你曾告诉我  如果你中了彩票
Well, yesterday you said if you ever win the lottery.
就带我去冒险天地的
You'd take me to super adventure land.
没错  出发吧  快上车
All right, let's go. Get in the car.
噢  等一下  等一下  我们可是百万富翁了
Oh, wait a minute. Wait a minute. We're millionaires.
哪还能开那辆破车  我们去租辆豪华轿车
Forget the car. We're renting a limo.
等一下  老爸
Wait, dad.
随便了
Okay.
噢  谢谢  查莉医生
Oh, thank you, Dr. Charlie.
我现在好多了
I'm all better now.
噢  还要打针啊
Ow. Another shot.
算了  我已经挨过七针了
No, I've already had seven shots.
我已经痊愈了
There's no more owies.
噢  又是一针
Ow. Another shot.
好了  我玩腻这个了
Okay, I think I'm kind of over this.
艾薇  可以准备走了吗
Ivy, are you ready to go?
看看俺在浴室发现了什么
Check out what I found in the bathroom...
钻石耳环
Diamond earrings.
瞧好吧
Watch me work it.
艾薇  嘿  快摘下耳环
Ivy, hey, take those off.
你可否知道迪迪的爸爸是新上任的副警长  道格·杜利
Don't you know that Deedee's daddy's deputy Doug Dooley?
艾薇·温茨戴着杜利的
Ivy Wentz rocking earrings.
收藏品耳环  楚楚动人
From the Dooley collection.
你没事吧  快摘下来
Seriously, take those off.
好吧  你戴上这东西应该更好看
Yeah, they'll look better on you anyway.
不成  我们是来照顾孩子的  不是来
No, we're here to babysit, not try on...
-好漂亮  -没错
-Ooh. -Yeah.
噢  的确很漂亮
Oh, these do look good.
没错  快打扮好自己  美女
Yep, strut your stuff, girl.
-很有趣的  快去  展示下  -好的
-It's fun. Go ahead, do it. -Okay.
噢  噢  噢  噢
Ooh ooh ooh ooh.
嗷  嘿  是谁仍的
Ow! Hey, who did that?
-噢  -怎么了
-Ooh. Uh-oh. -What?
有位医生打翻了一盒果汁
One of the doctors spilled a juice box.
而且俺希望那是果汁
At least I hope it's juice.
好了  艾薇  你去把他俩带外面去
All right, Ivy, why don't you take them outside?
我把这弄干净  然后我们就去“填充猴儿”
I'm gonna clean this up. And then we can go to make-a-monkey.
好的  来吧
Okay, come on.
过来  迪迪  该走了
Come on, Deedee. Let's go bye-bye.
和艾薇走
Go with Ivy.
-去“填充猴儿”喽  -耶
-Let's go to make-a-monkey. -Yay!
呦  果然不是果汁
Eww, and it's not juice.
-你要去哪  -呜
-Where are you going? -Whoa!
你在这里干什么
What are you doing here?
我告诉过你  我会一直盯着你的
I told you I was gonna be watching you.
你觉着我只是说说而已吗
Did you think I was a liar?
不是  我只是  我觉着你会在一定的距离之外盯着我
No, I just... I thought you'd be watching me from a distance...
比如用个单筒望远镜  或者双筒望远镜什么的
You know, with, like, a telescope or binoculars or something.
我的确这么做过一阵子  不过我看烦了
I did that for a while. I got bored.
现在我问你一个问题
Now I asked you a question.
你打算去哪
Where are you going?
呃  我打算去图书馆找斯凯勒
Uh, I'm going to the library to meet Skyler.
就这模样去了  你也不梳梳头发
Looking like that? You couldn't even comb your hair?
我可花了二十分钟才搞成这样的
I spent 20 minutes to get it like this.
你要干嘛
What are you doing?
只要你的行为  让我很不爽
Anytime you do something I do not like,
我就把它记在黑名单里
I mark it down in the negative column.
有白名单吗
Is there a positive column too?
目前没有
Not yet.
好吧
Okay.
好了  如果不介意
Well, if you'll excuse me,
我这就回去整理下我的头发
I'm gonna go back inside and comb my hair,
这并不是因为你的话影响到了我
But not because of anything you said...
而是我心甘情愿的
Because I want to.
不争气啊
Stupid.
“对门很粗鲁”
"bad with doors."
这四个小时真是够我受的
That was four hours of my life I'll never get back.
那首主题曲一直在我的脑海中挥之不去
I still have that theme song drilled into my head.
首先挑个颜色  棕色  绿色还是红色
<i>First you pick a color... brown or green or red</i>
然后找些东东  填满它的脑袋
<i>Then you take some stuffing and put it in its head</i>
然后还有二十多句  让你生不如死
<i>Then it goes on for 20 more verses and you wish you were dead</i>
这就是如何“填充猴猴猴儿”
<i>And that's how you make a mo-oh-oh-oh-nkey.</i>
-噢  不  -怎么了
-Oh no. -What?
耳环  你还戴着呢
The earrings... you're still wearing them.
-什么  -快看看吧
-What? -Yes.
噢  艾薇  艾薇  怎么就一只了
Oh! Ivy, Ivy, I just have one earring on.
-另外那只一定是掉哪了  -不是
-The other one must have fallen off. -No.
没错  没错  我弄丢了她的钻石耳环
Yes yes, I lost her diamond earring.
什么  那你当初为什么还要戴上试试啊
What? Why did you even try them on?
-什么  那是你出的主意  -你不会蠢到连我的话都听吧
-What? That was your idea! -You know better than to listen to me.
好了  好了  好了  大家不要慌
Okay okay okay okay. All right, let's not panic.
我只要  想到了  我去检查下车里
I'll just... okay, I'll check the car.
你  打电话问问“填充猴儿”那边有没有人发现耳环
You... you call make-a-monkey and see if they found it.
现在的当务之急就是
The important thing here is...
淡定
Is not to panic.
-车里没有  -那边也没有
-Not in the car. -Not at the place.
好吧  现在可以不淡定了  噢
Okay, time to panic. Oh!
冷静  俺有对策了
Calm down. Ivy's got a plan.
噢  你有对策了
Oh, Ivy's got a plan.
-听着  俺想俺知道耳环在哪  -在哪
-Look, I think I know where the earring is. -Where?
看看这个  俺在“填充猴儿”那里照了几张相片
Check it out. I took some pictures at make-a-monkey.
当时你站在填充机旁  还戴着两只耳环
Here you are at the stuffing machine... two earrings.
噢  噢  当我离开填充机后  就剩一只耳环了
Oh oh, here I am after the stuffing machine... one earring.
正解  所以丢失的耳环就在
Yes, so the missing earring is...
猴子里
Inside a monkey.
嗨  查莉  那抱着的是什么东西啊
Hi, Charlie. What you got there?
猴子
Monkey.
我能看看嘛
Can I see it?
-去拿猴子  -嗯嗯
-Get that monkey. -Mm-hmm.
天啊  你那妹妹
Man, that sister of yours.
跑得比刘翔还快
Can put up quite a fight.
我知道
I know.
幸好咱们抓的不是孙悟空
We'd be better off if we fought an actual monkey.
看来她真的喜欢这猴子
She sure does love that thing.
是啊  是啊  她的确喜欢
Yeah. Yeah, she sure does.
好了  快把它五马分尸了
Now let's rip it apart.
这里没有啊
It's not in here.
噢  这下完了  真的完蛋了
Oh, this is bad. This is really bad.
小泰  冷静
T, calm down.
如果耳环没在这只猴子里
If the earring isn't in this monkey,
那肯定在其它的猴子里
It has to be in the other monkey.
没错  没错  没错  在迪迪的猴子里
Right right right right, Deedee's monkey...
在一位警长的家里
That's in the police chief's house.
你看我够淡定吗
Is that calm enough for you?
天啊  冒险天地真是太爽了
Man, super adventure land was amazing.
绝对爽  嘿  嘿  再让我看看玩激流勇进时候的照片
It sure is. Hey hey, give me the picture of the log ride again.
-啊  看看你的表情  -还是看看你的吧
-Ah, look at your face. -Look at your face.
再看看豪华轿车司机的表情
Look at the limo driver's face.
好了  老爸  我们现在也乐够了
Okay, dad, now that we've had our fun,
有些事我也该和你谈下了
There's something I gotta tell you.
你还是先坐下吧
And maybe you should sit down.
嘿  乖儿子  快看看老娘的新坐骑
Hey, kids, how do you like mama's new ride?
嘿  看看你
Hey, look at you.
你从哪弄来的
Where did you get that?
在商场啊  没错  在你老爸说他中奖后
At the mall. Yeah, I did a little shopping.
我就去商场拼杀了
After your dad told me we won the lottery.
你能把这东西退了吗
You can return that, right?
没门儿  钞票手中握  不用再退货
Nope, forever rich has a no-return policy.
谁还为这事操心啊
But who cares?
反正不是我  百万富翁无忧无虑啊
Not me. Nothing bothers a millionaire.
百万富翁无忧无虑
Nothing bothers a millionaire.
-呜  呜  -呜
-Whoo-hoo! -Whoo!
实际上  你们并没有中彩票
You guys didn't really win the lottery.
这只是能够让我去冒险天地玩的一个诡计
It was just a prank so I could go to super adventure land.
别搞笑了
That's really funny.
你怎么不笑啊
So why aren't you laughing?
真的很抱歉  我未曾想过事情会到这种地步
I'm really sorry. I never meant for it to go this far.
我知道你很可能关我两周的禁闭
Now I know you're probably gonna ground me for, like, two weeks,
但在这种情况下
But under the circumstances,
关我三周都没问题
I'm fine with three.
我今天辞职了
I quit my job today.
什么
What?
还能复职  对吧
You can get it back, right?
呃
Uh...
什么  什么  中奖了  难以置信
What? What? We won? I can't believe it.
我告诉你令我难以置信的是什么  邓肯女士
I'll tell you what I can't believe, Duncan...
你又在接通私人电话
It's that you're taking another personal call.
我半小时前就让你
Now I asked you to do something.
处理下这些生理盐水
With these bags of saline a half an hour ago.
呃  先挂了
Uh, gotta go.
告诉你吧  卡伦  算你说对了
You know what, Karen? You're absolutely right.
很久以前我就应该处理掉
I should have done something with these saline bags.
这些生理盐水
A long time ago.
我是说  我早就应该这样了
I mean, this is really overdue.
-哦  哦  -耶  耶
-Oh! Oh! -Yeah yeah.
耶  耶
Yeah yeah.
嗨
Hi.
带我去康庄大道
Take me to easy street.
永别  窝囊废们
So long, suckers.
你怎能这样
How could you do that?
因为我是百万富翁啊
Because I was a millionaire.
富翁有富翁的生活之道
Rich people play by different rules.
我真的很抱歉
I'm so sorry.
老爸  你还好吧
Dad, are you okay?
怎么一直抱着爆米花啊
He's hugging the kettle corn.
现在除此我别无所有了
This is all I have left.
噢  陈皮笑脸总能让我开怀大笑
Oh, the old orange peel smile always cracks me up.
我上次试了一下菠萝皮的效果  就悲剧了
I tried it once with a pineapple... not as fun.
我去漱漱口
I gotta go rinse.
我受不了果肉塞我牙里的感觉
I can't stand the feel of pulp on my teeth.
我喜欢了解你的每一件事
I love learning new things about you.
-你没事吧  -我没事
-Is everything okay? -Everything's great.
-真的  -真的  没事
-Really? -Really, yeah.
好到  不能再好了
Everything... couldn't be better.
但你的行为有点儿怪异
You're acting kind of weird.
行为不怪异啊  一点儿也不
I'm not acting weird, no.
唯一怪异之处  就是我的表现一点儿也不怪异
If anything, I'm acting not weird.
-为什么总会发生这类的事情  -什么事情
-Why does this always happen? -What?
每当我和某个男生约会一段时间后
I date a guy for a while.
他们就突然变得怪怪的
And then all of a sudden he starts acting all strange.
那他们的下场如何
Then what happens?
人间蒸发了
Then he just kind of disappears.
嘿  老妈  你在干嘛
Hey, mom, what are you doing?
嘿  忙些事情  试着找份新工作
Hey. A couple things. Trying to find a new job.
还有查查把盖比送军校这件事
And researching military schools for Gabe.
哇  听着还挺有给力的
Wow, that sounds stressful.
嘿  知道吗  你应该去体育馆
Hey, you know, you should go to the gym,
也许  也许应该找一个伙伴儿一起锻炼
Maybe... maybe with a workout buddy,
比如杜比·杜利  她多幽默啊
Somebody like Debbie Dooley. She's fun.
泰迪  我知道你的意图是什么
Teddy, I know what you're trying to do.
没错  你想重新潜回杜利的家里
Mm-hmm, you want back into Debbie Dooley's house,
而且我还知道为什么
And I know why.
-你知道  -是的
-You do? -<i>Yep.</i>
你还想继续照顾孩子
You want another babysitting gig.
我就真的那么容易让人看穿吗
Am I that transparent?
查莉  你的猴子怎么了
Charlie, what happened to your monkey?
我也不知道
I don't know.
花了六十二块就做了这个破烂吗
$62 for this?
连脑袋的方向都不对
The head's not even facing the right way.
她就喜欢这造型的
That's the way she wanted it.
打扰一下  你是卡伦吗
Excuse me, are you Karen?
是的  什么事啊
Yeah. Why?
我叫盖比  是艾米·邓肯的儿子
I'm Gabe, Amy Duncan's son.
听着  我老妈辞职这件事  全是由于我的错误而引起的
Look, the reason my mom quit was all my fault.
我向父母玩了一个十分卑鄙的把戏
I played a really mean prank on my parents.
然后情况就一发不可收拾
And it got way out of hand.
现在你知道真相了  能把工作还给我老妈吗
Now that you know the truth, can you please give her her job back?
噢  那个
Oh, well,
如果这件事对于你那么重要的话
If it means that much to you,
没门儿
No!
哈  傻了吧
Ha! I gotcha!
噢  你真应该看看你的表情
Oh, you should see your face.
我把你骗得团团转  是不是
I really had you going there, didn't I?
噢  好样的  你真棒  卡伦
Oh good. Good for you, Karen.
好吧
Okay.
对不起
Excuse me,
你知道这是谁的彩票吗
Do you know whose lottery ticket this is?
知道  是我的
Yes. It's mine.
我中了  我中了
I won! I won!
我中了  我中了  我中了  我中了
I won, I won, I won, I won!
嘿  嘿  嘿
Hey hey hey!
我一直暗恋着你
I've always loved you.
嗨  需要  噢
Hi. May I...? Oh.
你还要审查我多久啊
How much longer are you gonna follow me around?
直到我弄清你是哪种人
Till I find out the kind of guy you are.
现在我是准备要续杯的那种人
Now I'm a guy who's about to restock the cups.
“对杯子很粗鲁”
"bad with cups."
听着  我弄得一团糟是因为你总是让我紧张
Look, I only messed up 'cause you made me nervous.
谢了
Thanks.
-审查结束了  -什么
-Got all I need. -For what?
去告诉斯凯勒你不是最佳人选
To tell Skyler you're not the guy.
再见
See ya.
等一下  站住
No no. Stop.
我就是最佳人选
I am the guy.
斯凯勒就是我生命中的唯一
Skyler is the best thing that's ever happened to me.
不论前方是多么的困难重重  我是不会退缩的
And I'm not going away, no matter what.
所以赶紧把这段话记在你那个小破本儿里
So put that in your little notebook.
噢  十二号  你的订餐好了  十二号
Oh, and number 12, your order's ready. Number 12.
惨了  是不是该到了把我弄消失的阶段了
Uh-oh. Is this the part where you make me disappear?
放松  孩子
Relax, kid.
你站出来为自己辩护  这才是我所想要听到的
You stuck up for yourself. That's what I wanted to hear.
这么说来我和你女儿约会这事  不反对了
So it's okay if I date your daughter?
噢  她不是我女儿
Oh, she's not my daughter.
是他的女儿
She's his daughter.
他一直雇佣我来审查男朋友
He always hires me to check out the boyfriends.
面带这么可爱的微笑  可做不了审查这项工作的
With that elfin smile, people don't take him too seriously.
泰迪又回去了  这可乐坏了迪迪
Deedee was so excited that Teddy was back.
你这个女儿还真是了不起啊
That daughter of yours is quite something.
是啊  我善于孕育了不起的女儿
Yeah, I make some good daughters.
鲍伯善于孕育不着调的儿子
Bob makes the boys.
昨天看见
Yesterday it was just so good.
泰迪和迪迪玩得真不赖
To watch deedee have fun with Teddy.
-看见  此话怎讲  -噢  那个
-What do you mean, watch? -Oh, well,
我老公坚持要放一个监控摄像头
My husband insisted we put in a nanny-cam.
噢  监控摄像头  我还没看见过呢
Oh, a nanny-cam? I've never seen one of those.
如果你有笔记本电脑  我现在就给你展示下
If you have a laptop, I'll show you right now.
我有  就在你背后  快看看
I do, right behind you. Let's look.
噢  好的
Oh good.
噢  看见了
Oh, there they are.
你女儿还真是有一套
Your daughter has a real gift.
我总是需要不停的哄迪迪才能睡下
It takes me forever to put deedee down.
这个  的确有点儿非同一般
Well, that's a little peculiar.
好像不对劲了
This doesn't seem right.
亲娘啊  她在杀害一只猴子
Oh my goodness, she's murdering the monkey.
-噢  -噢
-Oh. -Oh.
搞什么
Really?
一个邻居  我就想要一位邻居朋友啊
One neighbor... I just want to be friends with one neighbor.
嘿  查莉
Hey, Charlie.
听着  我今天学到了人生的重要一课
So I learned a very important life lesson today,
就是永远也不要带着
And that is never wear.
一副耳环去“填充猴儿”
A pair of accidentally make-a-monkey,
因为如果你戴了  你的邻居就可能说
Because if you do,your neighbor might said something like...
“亲娘啊
"oh my goodness,
那个女孩脑子有问题”
That girl's just not right in the head."
嗨  查莉
Hi, Charlie.
噢  还有老妈已经官复原职了
Oh, and mom's back at work.
其实是因为她的上司由于某种原因  就辞职了
Actually her boss quit for some unknown reason,
所以老妈还升职了
And so she got a promotion.
这就是为什么老爹我也弄了辆新坐骑
Which is why daddy gets one of these too.
鲍勃  小心前面啊
Bob, watch where you are going.
啊
<i>Ahh!</i>
噢
Oh.
是啊  几年后
Yeah, in a couple of years,
当我们这些孩子都离开家后
When all of us kids have left the house,
这一切都要你来承受了  好运喽  查莉
They'll be all yours. Good luck, Charlie.
嘿  你怎么了
Hey, what happened to you?
这还不够明显吗  我脑袋长反了
Isn't it obvious? My head's on backwards.
是啊  我也不用多说了
Yeah, I didn't want to say anything.
医生  病人已经准备好可以做手术了
Doctor, the patients are prepped and ready for surgery.
她看起来是不是还太小了
She look a little young to you?
我相信她是一位久经沙场的医生
I'm sure she's highly trained.
还是你先上吧
You can go first.